<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-02-29T19:42:13+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">I-LAMB</title><subtitle>The goal of the Robben lab is to develop the next generation of multi-omic sequencing technologies to investigate immune cell dysfunction in cancer and autoimmune disease. The future of high-throughput sequencing combines transcriptomics, proteomics, genomics and imaging into techniques like single cell RNA-seq and spatial transcriptomics. For the analysis of this data we need new computational methods utilizing machine learning algorithms that can identify patterns of cell interactions and differentiation.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Alexis and Zhixian join the Robben Lab!!!</title><link href="/2024/01/16/newstudents24.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Alexis and Zhixian join the Robben Lab!!!" /><published>2024-01-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-02-29T19:41:32+00:00</updated><id>/2024/01/16/newstudents24</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2024/01/16/newstudents24.html"><![CDATA[<p>The Robben lab is pleased to welcome Alexis Lindahl and Zhixian Bai to it’s ranks as new Ph.D. students in the department of Animal Science!</p>

<p>Alexis is a graduate of Indiana University Bloomington with a Bachelor’s degree in Biology. Alexis has previous experience working with GPCR pathways in a molecular and biochemistry lab and is coming on to gain more experience with cell and molecular research.</p>

<p>Zhixian is coming from Shenyang Agricultural University in China and graduated with a masters degree in Animal Science. Zhixian spent her masters studying the genetics of Goat wool properties and is joining the Robben lab to learn more about using Bioinformatic tools in research.</p>]]></content><author><name>Michael Robben</name></author><category term="New Members" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Robben lab is pleased to welcome Alexis Lindahl and Zhixian Bai to it’s ranks as new Ph.D. students in the department of Animal Science!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lab Grand Opening!</title><link href="/2023/08/16/open.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lab Grand Opening!" /><published>2023-08-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-02-29T19:41:32+00:00</updated><id>/2023/08/16/open</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/08/16/open.html"><![CDATA[<p>The Robben Lab/Illinois Laboratory for Animal Machine-learning and Bioinformatics (I-LAMB) is open for business!!!!</p>]]></content><author><name>Michael Robben</name></author><category term="Lab Update" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Robben Lab/Illinois Laboratory for Animal Machine-learning and Bioinformatics (I-LAMB) is open for business!!!!]]></summary></entry></feed>